Guide to the John R. Mott Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Photographs, Series X
  - Travel and conference photographs: chronologically arranged
    - Miscellaneous, 1900-1910 (Box 222, Folder 3466)
    - World trip for Continuation Committee, 1912-1913 (Box 222, Folder 3467)
    - Album: World tour, 1912-1913 (Box 222, Folder 3468)
    - Album: World tour, 1912-1913 (Box 223, Folder 3469)
    - WSCF conference--Princeton, 1913 (Box 223, Folder 3470)
    - Miscellaneous, 1914-1919 (Box 223, Folder 3471)
    - Mexican Commission, 1916 (Box 223, Folder 3472)
    - Mission to Russia, 1917 (Box 224, Folder 3473)
    - Album: Mission to Russia, 1917 (Box 224, Folder 3474)
    - Poland, 1920-1921 (Box 224, Folder 3475)
    - YMCA conference-Caux, 1920 (Box 224, Folder 3476)
    - Miscellaneous, 1920-1926 (Box 224, Folder 3477)
    - WSCF conference-Peking, 1922 (Box 224, Folder 3478)
    - Album: Manchuria, Palestine, Poland, Philippine Islands, c. 1924 (Box 224, Folder 3479)
    - IMC Moslem conferences, 1924 (Box 224, Folder 3480)
    - Related to Eastern Orthodox church, 1924-1935, n.d. (Box 224, Folder 3481)
    - Miscellaneous, 1927-1929 (Box 224, Folder 3482)
    - IMC Jerusalem conference, 1928 (Box 224, Folder 3483, Box OV1)
    - WSCF conference-Mysore, 1928 (Box 225, Folder 3484)
    - WSCF conference-Mysore, 1928 (Box 225, Folder 3485)
    - Japan, 1929, 1935 (Box 225, Folder 3486)
    - China, 1920's (Box 225, Folder 3487)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1935 (Box 225, Folder 3488)
    - Miscellaneous, 1936-1940 (Box 225, Folder 3489)
    - Albums: Uruguay ,Brazil, 1940 (Box 226, Folder 3490)
    - Miscellaneous, 1941-1947 (Box 226, Folder 3491)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948-1950 (Box 226, Folder 3492)
    - Miscellaneous, 1951-1955 (Box 226, Folder 3493)
    - Album: Far East, India (Box 226, Folder 3494)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 226, Folder 3495)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 226, Folder 3496)
  - Photographs occasioned by tributes to Mott: chronologically arranged
    - Reception in Toronto, 1935 (Box 227, Folder 3497)
    - Honorary degree, Upper Iowa University, 1943 (Box 227, Folder 3498)
    - Finnish decoration; Prince Karl medal, 1946 (Box 227, Folder 3499)
    - Nobel Prize, 1946, 1947 (Box 227, Folder 3500)
    - Memorial tablet in Washington Cathedral, 1958 (Box 227, Folder 3501)
    - Medals received, n.d. (Box 227, Folder 3502)
    - Reception of Viscount Shibasawa, n.d. (Box 227, Folder 3503)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 227, Folder 3504)
    - Miscellaneous negatives, n.d. (Box 227, Folder 3505)